<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Covid_Guide_App</string>
    <string name="open">open</string>
    <string name="close">close</string>
    <string name="yoga">" Anulom Vilom Pranayam or Alternate Nostril Breathing Technique of Yoga
        Method: Start by sitting in a cross-legged position. Rest your hands on your knees and close your eyes. Keep your right thumb on your right nostril and close it. Inhale deeply from your left nostril for 4 counts.
        Now close your left nostril with your right ring finger and hold it for 2 seconds. At this step, you are holding your breath with both your nostrils being closed. Take off your right thumb from your right nostril and exhale deeply through your right nostril.
        Inhale from your right nostril for 4 counts while continuing to keep your ring finger on your left nostril and then, close both nostrils for 2 seconds and exhale deeply with your left nostril. Repeat this process for 5 minutes. Concentrate on your breathing while doing it.
        Benefits: This breathing technique has a number of benefits like improving immune system, boosting your memory, improving respiratory and cardiovascular health and regulating blood pressure. This Yoga asana also improves sleep and helps to de-stress.
        As the ancient practice of controlling breath, Pranayama connects body and mind, supplies body with oxygen while removing toxins and is meant to provide healing physiological benefits. The stress-relieving effects of pranayama improves one’s sleep quality, increases mindfulness and reduces high blood pressure
        https://youtu.be/dVHIWLOgtmE"</string>

    <string name="call">CALL SOMEONE  source: https://healthblog.uofmhealth.org/wellness-prevention/5-ways-to-manage-your-mental-health-during-covid-19One of the most prominent ways individuals are asked to help mitigate the COVID-19 pandemic is to practice social distancing. That means remaining out of places where people meet or gather, and maintaining distance (approximately six feet or two meters) from others.
    In times of crisis, many people seek connection and comfort from others, says Kelcey Stratton, Ph.D., program manager for resilience and well-being services at Michigan Medicine, who is also a clinical psychologist. “It is important to find creative ways to maintain those connections. We might also find some comfort by remembering that we are not alone, and that we are all in this together to protect the health and well-being of our communities.”
    Create new traditions for connecting regularly with friends, family and peers via messaging apps, etc. Check in with your people. Call a family member, friend or coworker. Send a text message, direct message or email. Use FaceTime or other video formats to communicate.
    </string>
    <string name="Website">“Find a way to help others. A faith practice that is so critical is not simply an awareness of God’s love for you, but trying to give that love away, to share with others. So, I think about what practical things can I do to help people around me?”
    please share your valuable feedback on our website and catch up with the previous feedbacks given by other friends to overcome the infection. Thank You.
    </string>
    <string name="sleep">its time to sleep </string>
    <string name="dinner">A healthy dinner might give you a picture of bland and dull salads, flavourless bowls of food that might turn you off. Since the popular notion of healthy food remains to the date that it can not be delicious and appetising, we only think of boring dishes like a salad bowl, clear soups and anything that is tasteless. However, this is not really the case. You can eat healthy without compromising much on the taste and flavours because going healthy does not really mean banning all the carbs and fat from your diet. Indian cuisine is all about mouth-watering delicacies, packed with flavourful spices and herbs, cooked in oil and dollops of butter, and perhaps this is one of the reasons why we cannot imagine Indian food and healthy dinner together.
    CHICKPEA FLOUR PANCAKES This protein-rich instant dosa is perfect for dinner as it is full of veggies. Easy to make and you cannot overeat.
    </string>


</resources>